Guide to the Stanford University Audio Collection SC1074 SC1074
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University audio collection
circa 1949-2006
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University
SC1074
8.25 Linear Feet (16 boxes)
Audio recordings of Stanford events and activities.
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of audio recordings of Stanford events and activities.
Audiotapes.; Stanford University -- History.; Stanford University; Stanford University
- Audio recordings
  - Stolz, Lois: History of Women at Stanford, 1975; 1_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Clark, Birge: On site tour, discussion of faculty houses at Stanford. With Roxanne Nilan., 1980 Feb 12; 1_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Marston, John (fire chief, 1942-1970), 1986 Jun 25; 1_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Turner, Paul: Stanford quads and earlier campus plans. SHS. (tape 1 of 2), 1983 May 22; 1_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Turner, Paul: Stanford quads and earlier campus plans. SHS. (tape 2 of 2), 1983 May 22; 1_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Turner, Paul: Campus, 1985 Aug; 1_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Rogers, Everett: re: Silicon Valley, 1_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Hutchinson, Eric: Management development program; Hutchinson on history of Stanford administration., 1982 Oct 1; 1_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Hutchinson, Eric: Management development program; Hutchinson on history of Stanford administration., 1983 Oct 1; 1_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Hutchinson, Eric, 1984; 1_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Payne, Joe: ('33) Palo Alto Kiwanis; Stanford athletics., 1985 Feb 20; 1_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Packard, Martin: SHS Program re: Varian brothers, 1988 Dec 4; 1_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - SWOPSI 124: Medical Center (history-background). Side one: Drs. Cohn Melman; Side two: Dr. Alway., 1979 May 1; 1_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - SWOPSI 124: Medical Center (history-background). Side one: Dean Crowley., 1979 May 1; 1_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Nilan, Roxanne - Women, 1_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Stanford History, 1972 Nov 21; 1_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Winbigler, H.D.: "The agony and the ecstasy. Story on the 10/12-13/1980 inauguration. Talk at the Palo Alto Kiwanis club., 1980 Oct 23; 1_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Regnery, Dorothy: SHS program re Sacramento house., 1986 Mar 23; 1_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Jackson: On 1906 earthquake relief, 1_19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Ten years of President Lyman, 1_20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Howell, Lewis, Okimoto, Lewis., 1_21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Kennedy, Donald: Parents' Day, 1985 Oct 25; 1_22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Frederick Emmons Terman Memorial Service, 1983 Jan; 1_23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Arbuckle Memorial Service, 1986 Jan 24; 1_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Greenberg, Joespeh H.: Retirement Banquet Speech, 1985 Jun 10; 1_25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - MacKinnon, Robert: Chamber Cantata, 1_26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Weinberger, Casper: Speaking with 20 Stanford students, sponsored by ASSU Speaker's Bureau. Subjects included: draft, China, El Salvador, nuclear war, Reagan, administration's positions., 1982 Feb 12; 1_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Stegner, Wallace: The Pulitzer Prize winning novelist talks about writing novels and making characters believable. Reads from "Spectator Bird.", 1976 Dec 1; 1_28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Crook, Welton J., 1976 Jan 21; 1_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bacon, Rosamund, 1_30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bacon, Rosamund: Interview by Jeff Littleboy, 1983; 1_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Shumway, Norman, 1978, 1979; 1_33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Goldstein, Avram, 1_34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Vincenti, Walter G., 1986 May 12; 1_35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Bracewell, Ronald: On Halley's Comet, 1986; 1_32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Green, Cecil; Charette, Art, 1984 Mar 14; 1_36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Carson, Clay, 1_37; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Snitjer, Kate: Class of 1926, Daughter of Carl Lane Clemans, class of 1895. Interview by Dr. Lee Altenberg, 2_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - [Lois Meek Stolz?] interview, 2_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Linvill, John: re: Fred Terman and the Silicon Valley, 1984 Jul 26; 2_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Miles, Ferris, 1974 Nov 13; 2_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Jr.: Talk to the Stanford Historical Society Annual Meeting, 1981 May 30; 2_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Jr.: "My Father, Dr. Ray Lyman Wilbur." Palo Alto Historial Association General Meeting., 1989 Oct 1; 2_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Riggs: "Technology-Based Business: Can We Compete?", 2_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Hall, Robert: "Flat Tax.", 2_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Kirst, Mike: "Has Education's Promise to the Public Been Broken?", 2_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Tobin, James: Second annual Zale Lecture. Kresge Auditorium, Stanford University. Sponsor: School of Humanities and Sciences., 1982 May 12; 2_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Forum by Class of 1970 at 15th Reunion in 1985, 2_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Taubman, Philup: On Gorbachev, 1987 Apr 9; 2_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Rhodes, Frank: Centennial Convocation, 1985 Nov 11; 2_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Quad Dedication, 2_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Governor's Corner Dedication, 2_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Red Barn dedication, 2_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Stanford University's Centennial Years 1985-1991 - Opening Program., 1985 Mar 9; 2_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Werry, Kay (1 of 2), 1984 Jun 19; 2_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Werry, Kay (2 of 2) (Copy), 1984 Jun 19; 2_32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Calhoun, P (1 of 2), 1984 Jul 16; 2_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Calhoun, P (2 of 2), 1984 Jul 16; 2_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - YWCA, 1983 March; 2_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Davis, Angela: On Rape, 1983 Oct 4; 2_33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Centennial Program, 1985 Mar 9; 2_34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Retirement Dinner for Professor Joseph Greenberg, 1985 Jun 10; 2_35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Baccalaureate, 1983 Jun 11; 2_36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Dallin, 3_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Werry, Kay: YWCA (2 of 2), 1982 Jun 19; 3_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - L'Heureux, 3_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Glover, Frederic O. to Distaff, 1972 Jan 25; 3_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Glover, Frederic O. to Distaff, 1975 Jan 8; 3_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Gasparov, 3_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Peter Bing Dinner, 1981 May 11; 3_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - [Alice?], 3_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Tom Barclay Luncheon, 1982 Jan 31; 3_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Mosher, 3_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Osborne, Carol; Moser, Thomas, 3_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - [Auto-?], 3_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Historical Society Annual Meeting, 1986 May 25; 3_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Sula Lunch, 1985 May 22; 3_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - SULA Bag Lunch, 1985 May 22; 3_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Paret, Peter, 1982 Nov 11; 3_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Rick, John, 1986 Mar 3; 3_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Stanford Songs, The Stanford Band; The Stanford Chorus, 8_1; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 8)
  - Big Red Rose Bowl, 8_3; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 8)
  - The Incomparable Leland Stanford Junior University Marching Band, 1974; 8_4; 1 audio disc(s) (Box 8)
  - Song and drumming recorded at KZSU, 1962; 1 optical disc(s) (cd)
    Scope and Contents
    This recording was originally done in 1962 at the Stanford radio station, KZSU, for use as accompaniment for Williams’ dance performances.
    Biographical / Historical
    Timm Williams, a member of the Yurok Tribe, danced as Prince Lightfoot at Stanford games and rallies in the 1950s-60s.
    Yurok Indians -- Music.; Williams, Timm
  - Alan Manne memorial celebration, 2005; 1 optical disc(s) (cd)
    Alan S. Manne was on the faculty at Stanford University from 1961 until he retired in 1992, with the exception of two years teaching at Harvard (1974-76). He was known for devising economic models pertaining to major world concerns and the author of 128 papers and seven books
  - Taube press conference after winning Nobel, 4_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Retirement dinner, Cuthbertson, Augsberger and Glover. Speeches by R. Lyman and W. Sterling., 1977 Apr 11; 4_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Retirement dinner, Cuthbertson, Augsberger and Glover. Speeches by R. Lyman and W. Sterling., 4_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Banks, Paul: Slide show on preservation (Annenberg Auditorium), 1977 Oct 21; 4_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Brandin, Alf: Farewell dinner at Stanford (Part 1), 1971; 4_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Brandin, Alf: Farewell dinner at Stanford (Part 2), 4_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Brandin, Alf Sports Illustrated Award, 1961; 4_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Brandin, Alf: Stanford Achievment Award, 1979; 4_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Brandin, Alf: Stanford Retirement Dinner, 1971; 4_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Historical Society Annual Meeting, 1978 May 17; 4_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Cox, Alvin, San Francisco years of the Medical School, 1979-11-04; 4.11
  - Stanford Historical Society: Escondito Cottage talks, 1977 May 3; 4_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Glover, Frederic O.: Address to the Writers Section, Women's Faculty Club, 1979 Feb 7; 4_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Glover, Frederic O.: "Address to Distaff Club, "Stanford Adventures in the President's Office.", 1975 Jan 8; 4_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Jordan, David Starr: "The Spirit of Stanford" (a); Stanford University Band, Ernest Whitney Martin, Director (b), 1916, 1926; 4_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - King, Nikki: "The Stanford Museum: a talk given to the Stanford Historical Society.", 1978 Nov 6; 4_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Lyman, Richard: Campus Conference, 1975; 4_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Lyman, Richard: Dinner, 1976 June 10; 4_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Terman, Fred: Wireless Pioneer's Picnic, 1970; 4_19; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 4)
  - Stanford Historical Society, Annual Meeting. Includes Fred Glover and Ruth Scibird., 1979 May 29; 4_20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Robinson, Edgar E.: Memoirs (Sides 1, 2), 4_21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Robinson, Edgar E.: Memoirs (Sides 3, 4), 4_22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Robinson, Edgar E.: Memoirs (Sides 5, 6), 4_23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Terman, Frederick Emmons: Dinner, 1977 May 5; 4_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Terman, Frederick Emmons: Uncommon man award dinner, sponsored by Stanford Associates, 1978 Dec 7; 4_25; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - KZSU: Interview with Sharon Percy Rockefeller, 4_26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - KZSU Press Conference, 1972 May 2; 4_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Kennedy, Donald, et al.: Address to Freshmen, 1983 Sep 22; 4_28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Sterling, J. E. Wallace Memorial Service, 1985 July 9; 4_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Bond, Julian: On Martin Luther King, Jr., 1986; 4_30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Clark, Birge, 1984 May; 4_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - The Impact of Mexican Immigration on Chicano Communites: Albert Camarillo, Lionel Castillo, Carlos Vasquez, Gilberto Cardenas, Juan Gomez-Quinones, 5_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Intellectual and Public Life: Arturo Islas, Jean Franco, Carlos [P?], Carlos Monsivais, Hector Aguilar, 5_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Employment: Wayne Cornelius, Gustavo Del Castillo, Richard Mines, 5_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Border State Relations: Panel Discussion: U.S. - Mexico, 5_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Student Activism-Don Kennedy, Bob Beyers, 1985 Nov 11; 5_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Keynote Address: Gustavo Sainz, John Wirth, Jean Franco, Tomas Ybarra-Frausto, 5_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - RLG Project Meeting, 1983 Mar 10; 5_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - RLG Program, 1983 Mar 11; 5_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Burciaga on Goheen, 1986 Aug 18; 5_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Kaplan on Goheen, 1986 Jul 14; 5_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - S. [S?] on Goheen, 1986 Aug 11; 5_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Barbour on Goheen, 1986 Aug 25; 5_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Siegel on Goheen, 1986 Aug 20; 5_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Fetter on Goheen, 1986 Aug 13; 5_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - WHC-RF Bacchetti A: Dart. years. B: More Dart. NYC Job. Chicago, 1977 Aug 21, 1977 Sep 10; 5_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Maxine Anderson on Christine Ricker, 1986 Oct 17; 5_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Maxine Anderson on Christine Ricker, 1986 Oct 17; 5_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Brown, R. M., 1987 Jul 1; 5_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Goheen, John, 1987 Jan 20; 5_19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Harvey Hall on Ombudsman's Office; John Goheen, 1986 Jul 17; 5_20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Jordan, Payton, 5_21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Krauskopf, K., 1986 Dec 4; 5_22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Krauskopf, K., 1987 Jan 13; 5_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Stanford Historical Society Program: Dorothy Regnery re Sacramento House, 1986 Mar 23; 5_26; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Latin American Panel, 1983 Jan 14; 5_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Cowley, William H., 1977 Jan 26; 5_28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Dorothy Regnery; Sister Mary Anne Bonpane; Linda Long at Stanford Sacramento House, 1985 Jan 18; 5_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Cowley, 1977 Feb 7; 5_30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Korff - WHC Concepts, 1975 Jul; 5_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Korff - People Known by WHC, 1975 Jul 23; 5_32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Review with Art Glogau of the present status of my thinking about my work and future plans., 1973 Dec; 5_33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Commencement Frost (1 of 2), 1983 Jun 12; 5_34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Commencement Frost (2 of 2), 1983 Jun 12; 5_35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - Memorial Service for V. K. Whitaker, 1984 Apr 11; 5_36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 7)
  - Herring, Conyers: "From Coffee Breaks to Library Budgets, Communications among Scientists.", 1989 Jun 6; 6_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Binning, Dennis: 1st tape of early 1969 Interview., 6_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Binning, Dennis: 2nd tape of early 1969 Interview., 6_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Interview by former student Robert Bersi about some WHC Concepts, 6_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - WHC-Description of collections and tentative plan for deciding what to do with them, 1973 Jul 23; 6_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Art Glogau of Carnegie Book versions (tape 1), 1973 Dec; 6_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Art Glogau of Carnegie Book versions (tape 2), 1973 Dec; 6_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Michael Korff of The Cowley Collections, 1975 Jul 4-7; 6_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Michael Korff of The Cowley Collections, 1975 Jul 7; 6_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Michael Korff of various WHC publishing efforts, 1975 Jul; 6_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Michael Korff of various WHC publishing efforts and books, 1975 Jul; 6_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Review with Art Glogau of Student Personal Writings, 1973 Dec; 6_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Cowley, W. M., 1976 Dec 20; 6_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - WHC, RFB, Mosher Conversation about WHC's collections., 1976 Jan 29; 6_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - WHC-JBH: Evolution of courses and workbooks, 1977; 6_15; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Cowley, 6_16; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Discussion with Michael Korff of method of WHC dissertation supervision (and efforts to get students' disserations published)., 1975 Jul; 6_17; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - WHC-Mike Korff. Writing efforts., 1975 Jul; 6_18; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - WHC and Dartmouth Pres. E. M. Hopkins, 1919-1942, to Nora Winnick, 1973 Jul 23; 6_19; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Jacobsen, David: Taped inserts for transcript, 6_20; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Glover to Rotary, 1975 Oct 6; 6_21; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Fred Glover on overseas campus, 1979 Feb 1; 6_22; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Fred Glover - Stanford History, 1972 Nov 11; 6_23; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Lyman dinner for Wally Sterling, 1976 May 8; 6_24; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - The Chancellor Sterling reception, Stanford Faculty Club, 1979 Apr 15; 6_27; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Buchanan, Bruce: Artificial Intelligence, 6_28; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Bailey, M.: 12th Night; Acting lecture fragments, 6_29; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Hoover, Theodore, 1981 Jul 28; 6_30; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - SHS Tape II, 1983 May 19; 6_31; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - SHS Meeting, 1983 May 19; 6_32; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Walker, Robert: Overseas Studies Program (SHS Program), 1983 Apr 17; 6_33; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Osborne, Carol: SHS, 1984Nov 18; 6_34; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Kirk, William: History of SLAC, 6_35; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Kirk, William: History of SLAC, 1984May; 6_36; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 6)
  - Glover: Distaff Club, 1983 Mar 13; 1 audiocassette(s)
  - Law School ground-breaking ceremony (1 of 3), 1972; 12_1; 1 dictation belt(s) (Box 12)
  - Law School ground-breaking ceremony (2 of 3), 12_2; 1 dictation belt(s) (Box 12)
  - Law School ground-breaking ceremony (3 of 3), 12_3; 1 dictation belt(s) (Box 12)
  - Williams, Timm, song and drumming recorded at KZSU, 1962; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) (Box 9U)
  - Manne, Alan, memorial celebration, 2005 Oct 30; 1 optical disc(s) (cd) 1 optical disc(s) (DVD) (Box 11U, Box 10U)
  - [No title], 13_1; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - [No title], 13_2; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Peter Bing Dinner (copy 1), 13_3; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Peter Bing Dinner (copy 2), 13_4; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Peter Bing Dinner (copy 3), 13_5; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Peter Bing Dinner (copy 4), 13_6; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Bracewell, Ronald - Tree Tour (1 of 2), 1980 Jun 7; 13_7; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Bracewell, Ronald - Tree Tour (2 of 2), 1980 Jun 7; 13_8; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Trader Vic's, 13_9; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Anna Lev - Interview (1 of 2), 1980 Nov 17; 13_10; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Anna Lev - Interview (2 of 2), 1980 Nov 17; 13_11; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Rosenzweig, Robert, 1983 Jan 28; 13_12; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - RLG Project Meeting, 1983 Mar 10; 13_13; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - RLG Program, 1983 Mar 11; 13_14; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 13)
  - Intermezzo, 66:10:6, Ralph Hansen, 14_1; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Meyer Library - Tape 1, 1969 Apr 30; 14_2; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Meyer Library - Tape 2, 1969 Apr 30; 14_3; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Meyer Library - Tape 3, 1969 Apr 30; 14_4; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Dedication Ceremonies - Stanford in Britain, 14_5; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Matlovich, Leonard - Gay Activist and former Air Force Sargeant Speaking at Stanford University, 1975 Dec 9; 14_6; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Gay Life Styles, 1975; 14_7; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Brainstorm, 1974 Sep 24; 14_8; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - KZSU 9:30p.m. Mary Hanson and Bob Bose.re Department of Defense and in reply to Dr. Lyman's speech - to 10:15p.m.; 10:15p.m. Lyman speech rebroadcast., 14_9; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - KSFO Radio, SF: Hubert Humbrey at Stanford, 1967 Feb 26; 14_10; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - KCBS Radio, SF: VP Humphrey at Stanford - Excerpts of activity outside hall before and after appearance. Report by Bob Vainowski., 1967 Feb 20; 14_11; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Lyman, Richard W., 14_12; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - DeGuerre pools and courts dedication. Lyman., 1974 Feb 23; 14_13; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Law School groundbreaking, 1972 Aug 11; 14_14; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Plaque Ceremony of the Hanna House as Frank Lloyd Wright memorial by the American Institute of Architects, Stanford Summer Festival., 1966 Jul 9; 14_15; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Moffat Interviews: Henry Kaplan, William Dement, Dan Okeefe, Martin Scharf, A. Schewttman., 1973-1976; 14_16; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Moffat Interviews: A. Schewttman, 1974; 14_17; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Moffat Interviews: A. Schewttman, Ginzton, Boyd, Bagshaw, 1974; 14_18; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Emile Billet "Bodie" (1 of 2), 1970 Jan 12; 14_19; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Emile Billet "Bodie" (2 of 2), 1970 Jan 12; 14_20; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Dr. Goldman Lecture - Truman and Eisenhower, 14_21; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Dr. Eric Goldman Lecture VII, 14_22; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Dr. Eric Goldman Lecture #6 "The 1920s and 1930s", 1962 Jul 30; 14_23; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - History of Stanford, narrated by Ralph Hansen., 1971; 14_24; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Stanford Solar Observatory Dedication. Art, Aud., 1974 Apr 26; 14_25; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - 1972 Senior Class: June 10 in Mem Aud., 1972 Jun 10; 14_26; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Address by SU President Richard Lyman, Tresidder Memorial Union, 1975 Nov 12; 14_27; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - President Richard Lyman, Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 1974 Oct 28; 14_28; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - President Lyman's State of the University Address, Dinkelspiel Auditorium, 1974 Jan 17; 14_29; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Joshua Lederberg, "Man looks at his own evolution." Stanford Alumni Conference., 1965 May 22; 14_30; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - President Lyman Daniel Patrick Moynihan, Frost Amphitheatre, 1965 Jun 15; 14_31; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Institute of American History Conference on the Civil War, The Crisis of the Union, 1860-1861: Why the Republican Party Rejected Both Compromise and Secession. Chariman: Thomas A. Bailey; Paper: David M. Potter; Comment: Kenneth M. Stampp., 1963 Mar 2; 14_33; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Institute of American History Conference on the Civil War, The Crisis of the Union, 1860-1861: Why the Democratic Party Divided. Chairman: Edgar E. Robinson; Paper: Roy F. Nichols; Comment: Robert W. Johannsen, 1963 Mar 2; 14_32; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Dr. Eric Goldman Lecture #4 "What Was Not Compromised.", 1962 Jul 16; 14_34; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Kaplan, Henry, 14_35; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - EYAWTRAS #1, 14_36; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 14)
  - Thai Ambassador, Sukich Nimmanheminda, adresses the Stanford University Club of Washington about "Stability of Thailand in Southeast Asia", 15_01_15_02; 2 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
  - Frank Albert interviews members of the Stanford University Club of Washington at the residence of Thai Ambassador Sukich Nimmanheminda, 15_03_15_04; 2 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
  - Spouse Quarter Lecture Series
    - Dement, William C., 1972 Oct 24; 15_05; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)
    - Bem, Sandra, "Development of Sex Roles", 1973 Oct 2; 15_06; 1 audiotape reel(s) (Box 15)